It must have been about two in the morning when I returned home.
I tried to wake up my wife by ringing the doorbell, but she was fast asleep, so I got a ladder from the shed in the garden, put it against the wall, and began climbing towards the bedroom window.
I was almost there when a sarcastic voice below said, 'I don't think the windows need cleaning at this time of the night.'
I looked down and nearly fell off the ladder when I saw a policeman.
I immediately regretted answering in the way I did, but I said, 'I enjoy cleaning windows at night.'
'So do I,' answered the policeman in the same tone.
'Excuse my interrupting you.
I hate to interrupt a man when he's busy working, but would you mind coming with me to the station?'
'Well, I'd prefer to stay here,' I said.
'You see.
I've forgotten my key.'
'Your what?'
he called.
'My key,' I shouted.
Fortunately, the shouting woke up my wife who opened the window just as the policeman had started to climb towards me.